insightssuccess.in 2018-06-08

# Insights Success - Privacy Policy - Insightssuccess.in

**Insights Success Privacy Policy:** Succeeding Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Insights success media and technology pvt ltd collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the <http://www.insightssuccess.com/> website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Insights success media and technology pvt ltd.

**Personal identification information:** We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Web browser cookies:** Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

  * To improve customer service: Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * To personalize user experience: we may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  *  To run a promotion contest survey or other Site featureto send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * To send periodic emails: we may use the email address to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. If user decides to opt-in to our mailing list they will receive emails that may include company news updates related product or service information etc. If at any time the user would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information:** We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

**Sharing your personal information:** We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Advertising:** Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Changes to this privacy policy:** Success media and technology pvt ltd has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email or may not. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms:** By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**A note to add on:** The Web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we’ll post the changes before they take effect. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

**How to connect with us:** If you have any questions regarding our privacy statement, please feel free to contact us by e-mail at [info@insightssuccess.com.](http://info@insightssuccess.com./)
